Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Publishing Files
  - Illich, Ivan
    - Celebration of Awareness - reviews, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Celebration of Awareness - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Celebration of Awareness - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Tools for Conviviality - correspondence and files, 1976-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Tools for Conviviality - reviews, 1982-1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Tools for Conviviality - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Right to Useful Unemployment - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Limits to Medicine - correspondence and files, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19-20)
    - Limits to Medicine - reviews, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Limits to Medicine - cover proofs, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Limits to Medicine - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - School into Museum - typescript, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Unknown typescript, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
    - Author file, undated (Box 17, Folder 26-28)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Imog, Jo
    - The Demon Flower - correspondence and files, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Demon Flower - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Ireland, David
    - A Woman of the Future - correspondence and files, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Ives, Charles
    - Memos - reviews, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Essays Before a Sonata - reviews, 1969-1996 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Essays Before a Sonata - correspondence and files, 1976-1981 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Jamieson, Alison
    - The Heart Attacked - reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Janacek, Leos
    - Uncollected Essays on Music - correspondence and files, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Uncollected Essays on Music - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Uncollected Essays on Music - reviews, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Jardim, Anne
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jenkins, Hugh
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Culture Gap - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Joans, Ted
    - A Black Pow-Wow of Jazz Poems - reviews, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - A Black Pow-Wow of Jazz Poems - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Afrodisia - correspondence and files, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Afrodisia - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - A Black Manifesto in Jazz Poetry and Prose - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jodorowsky, Alexandro
    - El Topo - reviews, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - El Topo - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Jones, Leroi (Amiri Baraka)
    - Four Black Revolutionary Plays - reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Four Black Revolutionary Plays - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Four Black Revolutionary Plays - correspondence and files, 1980-1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Four Black Revolutionary Plays - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Jouve, Nicole Ward
    - The Streetcleaner - correspondence and files, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - The Streetcleaner - reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Streetcleaner - cover proofs and drafts, 1988? (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Author file, 1984-1996 (Box 18, Folder 18-19)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Jupp, Kenneth
    - A Chelsea Trilogy - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - Kael, Pauline
    - Taking It All In - correspondence and files, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Taking It All In - reviews, 1984-1987 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Going Steady - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Going Steady - correspondence and files, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - 5001 Nights at the Movies - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Deeper Into the Movies - reviews, 1973-2000 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Deeper Into the Movies - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Reeling - correspondence and files, 1977-1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - I Lost It at the Movies - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - State of the Art - reviews, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - State of the Art - correspondence and files, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Raising Kane - correspondence and files, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 32-33)
    - Raising Kane - cover proofs, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Raising Kane - reviews, 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Movie Love - reviews, 1991-2001 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Kiss Kiss Bang Bang - cover proofs, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Kiss Kiss Bang Bang - correspondence and files, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Kiss Kiss Bang Bang - reviews, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Kiss Kiss Bang Bang - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Hooked - cover proofs, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Hooked - correspondence and files, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Hooked - cover drafts, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - When the Lights Go Down - correspondence and files, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - When the Lights Go Down - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Obituaries, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kaffka, Margit
    - The Ant Heap - reviews, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The Ant Heap - correspondence and files, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kalich, Richard
    - The Cry of the Cat - reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Cry of the Cat - correspondence and files, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Cry of the Cat - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Kane, Eileen and Mary O'Reilly-de Brun
    - Doing Your Own Research - reviews, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Doing Your Own Research - cover proofs, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Kane, Eileen
    - Author file, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Kantor, Brian
    - Understanding Capitalism - typescript, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Understanding Capitalism - correspondence and files, 1994? (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Kantor, Tadeusz
    - Wielopole/Wielopole - correspondence and files, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
    - Wielopole/Wielopole - photographs and artwork, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Kaye, David
    - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Keller, Nora Okja
    - Comfort Woman - reviews, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Comfort Woman - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Fox Girl - reviews, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Fox Girl - cover proofs, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Author file, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Kelly, Robert
    - The Scorpions - reviews, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Kenner, Hugh
    - Photographs, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - A Homemade World - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - Kesey, Ken
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - reviews, 1998-2009 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - cover drafts, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - correspondence and files, 1977-2009 (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
    - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Obituaries, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Khalap, Kiran
    - Halfway Up the Mountain - reviews, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Klein, Mavis
    - How to Choose a Mate - reviews, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - How to Choose a Mate - correspondence and files, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - How to Choose a Mate - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Pain and Joy in Intimate Relationships - correspondence and files, 1992? (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Pain and Joy in Intimate Relationships - reviews, 1991-2009 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Pain and Joy in Intimate Relationships - cover drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Klinkowitz, Jerome
    - Their Finest Hours - cover drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Their Finest Hours - reviews, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Their Finest Hours - correspondence and files, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Klossowski, Pierre
    - Roberte Ce Soir - correspondence and files, 1981-1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Roberte Ce Soir - reviews, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Roberte Ce Soir - cover proofs, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Koch, Stephen
    - Stargazer - reviews, 1974-1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Stargazer - correspondence and files, 1983-2002 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
    - Nightwatch - correspondence and files, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Nightwatch - reviews, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Nightwatch - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - The Bachelor's Bride - reviews, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Korbol, Aud
    - Tenement Waltz - typescript, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Kothari, Manu & Lopa Mehta
    - Death - correspondence and files, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Death - reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Cancer - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1981-1993 (Box 20, Folder 20-21)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Kristeva, Julia
    - About Chinese Women - cover proofs, undated (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Kronkhausen, Phyllis & Eberhard
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Lamott, Anne
    - Hard Laughter - cover drafts, undated (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Hard Laughter - reviews, 1980-1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Hard Laughter - correspondence and files, 1989-1997 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Hard Laughter - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - Lange, Monique
    - The Bathing Huts & Cannibals in Sicily - reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - The Bathing Huts & Cannibals in Sicily - typescript and page proofs, undated (Box 20, Folder 30-31)
    - The Bathing Huts & Cannibals in Sicily - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - The Bathing Huts - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Leante, Luis
    - See How Much I Love You - cover proofs, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Seee How Much I Love You - reviews, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Leiss, William
    - Limits to Satisfaction - correspondence and files, 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Limits to Satisfaction - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Le Parrier, Hubert
    - The Doctor from Cordova - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Liaut, Jean-Noel
    - Cover Girls & Supermodels - reviews, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Cover Girls & Supermodels - correspondence and files, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lilly, John C.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Litt, Toby
    - Beatniks - reviews, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Beatniks - cover proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitionism - reviews, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Corpsing - reviews, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Corpsing - correspondence and files, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Corpsing - cover proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Lonn, Oystein
    - Tom Reber's Last Retreat - reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Tom Reber's Last Retreat - incomplete typescript, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Tom Reber's Last Retreat - cover drafts and artwork, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Tom Reber's Last Retreat - correspondence and files, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Lorca, Federico Garcia
    - Selected Letters - cover proofs and artwork, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Selected Letters - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Selected Letters - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Deep Song - correspondence and files, 1982-1991 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Deep Song - cover drafts, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Deep Song - cover proofs, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Deep Song, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Marceau, Felicien
    - Creezy - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Maconie, Robin
    - Stockhausen - correspondence and files, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Stockhausen - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
  - Macsweeney, David
    - Once Upon A Time - typescript, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - Madden-Simpson, Janet
    - Woman's Part - reviews, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Magun, Carol
    - Circling Eden - typescript, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Mahon, James
    - An Introduction to the Study of Practical Ethics - correspondence and files, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Mallea, Eduardo
    - All Green Shall Perish - reviews, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - All Green Shall Perish - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Chaves - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Mann, Klaus
    - Siblings - reviews, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Siblings - correspondence and files, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Siblings - cover drafts and artwork, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Siblings and the Children's Story - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Distinguished Visitors - typescript, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
  - Manning, Rosemary
    - A Time & A Time - reviews, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - A Time & A Time - correspondence and files, 1981-1995 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Margulies, Edward & Stephen Rebello
    - Bad Movies We Love - reviews, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Marowitz, Charles
    - Potboilers - reviews, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - The Shrew - correspondence and files, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Prospero's Staff - reviews, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Wilde West - typescript, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Dickhead - typescript, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - The Sherlock Log - typescript, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Marowitz Shakespeare - correspondence and files, 1978-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - The Marowitz Shakespeare - cover proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - The Marowitz Shakespeare - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - Sex Wars - typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Sex Wars - reviews, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Sex Wars - correspondence and files, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Sex Wars - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Artaud at Rodez - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Matura, Mustapha
    - "As Time Goes By" - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - McDonald, Robert
    - Pillar & Tinderbox - reviews, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Author file, 1981-1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - McKnight, John
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - McLean, Allan Campbell
    - The Glasshouse - reviews, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - McMaster, Rhyll
    - Feather Man - reviews, 2007-2009 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Feather Man - cover proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - McMillan, Dougald
    - Transitions - artwork and photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Mechanicus, Philip
    - Waiting for Death - reviews, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Waiting for Death - correspondence and files, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Mehta, Lopa
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Meyer, Ernst H.
    - Early English Chamber Music - cover proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Early English Chamber Music - correspondence and files, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Early English Chamber Music - page proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Early English Chamber Music - reviews, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Meyer, Niels & Helveg Petersen & Villy Sorensen
    - Revolt from the Center - page proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Revolt from the Center - correspondence and files, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Revolt from the Center - reviews, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Revolt from the Center - cover proofs, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Author file, 1981-1996 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Meynell, Katharine & Alistair Skinner
    - It's Inside - reviews, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Michael, Ib
    - Kilroy Kilroy - typescript, undated (Box 22, Folder 34-35)
  - Miles Jr., Rufus E.
    - Awakening from the American Dream - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - Milhaud, Darius
    - Correspondence regarding illustrations, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - My Happy Life - correspondence and files, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
    - My Happy Life - reviews, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Henry
    - Tropic of Cancer - correspondence and files, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Mitchison, Naomi
    - Not by Bread Alone - correspondence and files, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Not by Bread Alone - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1982-1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Moll, Lane de & Gigi Coe
    - Stepping Stones - cover proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Stepping Stones - correspondence and files, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Montale, Eugenio
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Poet in Our Time - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
  - Morley, Dave & Ken Worpole
    - The Republic of Letters - reviews, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Morris, Edita
    - Love to Vietnam - reviews, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Mosley, Philip
    - Ingmar Bergman - cover proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Ingmar Bergman - cover proofs (Box 74 (oversize))
  - Mottram, Eric
    - William Burroughs - cover proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - William Burroughs - reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - William Burroughs - correspondence and files, 1976-1984 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Mullarney, Maire
    - Anything School Can Do… - reviews, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Nadal, Rafael Martinez
    - Lorca's the Public - reviews, 1974-1988 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Lorca's the Public - correspondence and files, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Author file, 1983-1999 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Nectoux, Jean-Michel
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Gabriel Faure - correspondence and files, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Gabriel Faure - cover drafts & artwork, undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Gabriel Faure - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Nersesian, Arthur
    - Chinese Takeout - cover proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Newman, Charles
    - New Axis or all about 'Little Ed' - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Norris, Christopher
    - Shostakovich - correspondence and files, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Novarra, Virginia
    - Women's Work, Men's Work - reviews, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Women's Work, Men's Work - correspondence and files, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 31-32)
    - Women's Work, Men's Work - page proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Nuttall, Jeff
    - Snipe's Spinster - correspondence and files, 1976? (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Snipe's Spinster - reviews, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Nye, Robert
    - Tales I Told My Mother - reviews, 1982-1993 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Tales I Told My Mother - cover drafts, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Tales I Told My Mother - correspondence and files, 1992? (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Darker Ends - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
    - Penthesilea - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
  - O'Brien, Kate
    - Author file, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - O'Brien, Tim
    - Northern Lights - correspondence and files, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Northern Lights - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - If I Die in a Combat Zone - cover drafts, undated (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - If I Die in a Combat Zone - correspondence and files, 1986-1988 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - If I Die in a Combat Zone - cover proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - If I Die in a Combat Zone - reviews, 1973-1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - If I Die in a Combat Zone - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Odent, Michel
    - Entering the World - correspondence and files, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
    - Entering the World - cover proofs, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Entering the World - cover drafts & artwork, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Entering the World - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo
    - Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness - page proofs, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness - correspondence and files, 1978-1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness - cover proofs, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Hiroshima Notes - correspondence and files, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Hiroshima Notes - cover proofs, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Hiroshima Notes - reviews, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Hiroshima Notes - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Nip the Buds, Shoot the Kids - reviews, 1983-1995 (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
    - Nip the Buds, Shoot the Kids - correspondence and files, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
    - Nip the Buds, Shoot the Kids - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
    - M/T - correspondence and files of translator John Nathan, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Olson, Toby
    - Seaview - correspondence and files, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Seaview - page proofs, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Omond, Tamsin
    - Rush - reviews, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Rush - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Rush - correspondence and files, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Ondaatje, Michael
    - Rat Jelly - correspondence and files, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Coming Through Slaughter - correspondence and files, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - The Collected Works of Billy the Kid - correspondence and files, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Ouellette, Fernand
    - Edgard Varese - reviews, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Page, Edwin
    - Quintessential Tarantino - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Quintessential Tarantino - reviews, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Gothic Fantasy - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Horribly Awkward - reviews, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Palmer, Christopher
    - The Composer in Hollywood - correspondence and files, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
    - The Composer in Hollywood - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Author file, 1989-1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Paquot, Thierry
    - The Art of the Siesta - reviews, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - The Art of the Siesta - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Author file, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Parmelin, Helene
    - Art Anti-Art - cover proofs, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Art Anti-Art - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Parra, Nicanor
    - Emergency Poems - correspondence and files, 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Emergency Poems - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))